http://www.ybcl.org/privacy/

Privacy Policy
On this Web site we try to ensure your privacy. We collect only personal information provided by you on a voluntary basis, in order to respond to your queries and to send you any additional information and material that you request.
Visitors to this Web site are not tracked, except to produce aggregate statistical data that does not identify individual users. Where we must use cookies to provide essential functionality, these are not used to track your use of the site or to store personally identifiable information. Steps have been taken to ensure that all information collected from you will remain secure, free from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Please keep in mind that if you leave this site via a link, the other site may have a different policy regarding privacy.
We occasionally update this privacy policy and encourage you to review it periodically. If you wish to correct your personal information, or have questions regarding this policy, please send an email message to admin@ybcl.org e-mail address.
Thinking about hiring our facilities? We’d love to hear from you!
Enquire now
Quick Links Australian Bahá’í Community
International Bahá’í Community
Online Child Protection Refresher Course
Bahá'í Investment Fund
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Inspiring Quotes
Regard man as a mine rich in gems of inestimable value. Education can, alone, cause it to reveal its treasures, and enable mankind to benefit therefrom.
The Baha’i Writings
Upcoming Events Kidz for Peace
November 23-25, 2018
National Summer School
January 25-29, 2019
About YBCL 27 Sierra Street,
© 2016 National Spiritual Assembly of the Bahá'ís of Australia Inc.
